betterdoctor.com 2016-12-01

# Privacy Policy | BetterDoctor

## Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes our policies on the collection, use, and disclosure of your information in connection with your use of BetterDoctor’s websites and mobile applications (the "Services"). The terms "we", "us", and "BetterDoctor" refer to BetterDoctor Inc., a Delaware corporation. Capitalized terms used but not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meanings ascribed to them in the Terms of Use. When you use the Services, you consent to our collection, use, and disclosure of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

## 1\. Information Collection

We collect information from you in several different ways while providing the Services. 

We may collect following information: 

#### 1.1 Personal Information

In order for you to access certain features of the Services, we may require you to provide us with certain information that personally identifies you (“Personal Information”). Personal Information includes the following categories of information: (1) Contact Data (such as your e-mail address, phone number and BetterDoctor password); (2) Demographic Data (such as your gender, your date of birth and your zip code); (3) Insurance Data (such as your insurance carrier and insurance plan); (4) Medical Data (such as your previous health care providers visited, your reason for visit and your date of visit); and (5) other information you choose to share with us. If you communicate with us by, for example, e-mail or letter, any information provided in such communication may be collected as Personal Information. 

We will never ask you to provide, request that you do not provide, and disclaim all liability if you chose to provide any information that relates to the past, present, or future physical or mental health or condition of an individual; the provision of health care to an individual; or the past, present, or future payment for the provision of health care to an individual (collectively, “Individually Identifiable Health Information”). Providing any such information may be grounds for termination from use of the Services. 

#### 1.2 Location

We may collect and store information about your location if you enable your computer or mobile device to send us location information. You may be able to change the settings on your computer or mobile device to prevent it from providing us with such information. 

#### 1.3 Activity

We may collect and store information related to you and your use of the Services, such as your browser type, IP address, unique device identifier, the phone numbers and names of businesses that you call through use of the Services, requested URL, referring URL, browser language, the pages you view, and the date and time of your visit. 

We may also use third party analytics services in connection with the Services. For example, we may use services to record mouse clicks, mouse movements, scrolling activity, and/or clicks to call or contact health care providers through the Services, as well as any text that you type into the Services (collectively, “Traffic Data”). These analytics services will not collect Personal Information that you do not voluntarily enter. These services will not track your browsing habits across websites which do not use their services. We are using the information collected from these services to find usability problems to make the Services easier to use. The recordings will never identify you or your account. We only record anonymous user information, and we stop such recording before you sign-in or create an account. Should we decide to use any third party analytics services that track or collect Personal Information, we will provide you with advance notice. 

#### 1.4 Cookies and Similar Mechanisms

“Cookies” are small computer files that are transferred to your computer's hard drive that contain information such as user ID, user preferences, lists of pages visited and activities conducted while browsing the Services. At your option, expense and responsibility, you may block cookies or delete cookies from your hard drive. However, by disabling cookies, you may not have access to the entire set of features of the Services. 

We may use cookies, web beacons, local shared objects (sometimes called flash cookies), and similar technology in connection with your use of the Services. Cookies may have unique identifiers, and reside, among other places, on your computer, in emails we send to you, and on our web pages. Cookies may transmit information about you and your use of the Services, such as your browser type, search preferences, data relating to advertisements that have been displayed to you or that you have clicked on, and the date and time of your use. 

#### 1.5 Information Provided on Behalf of Children

BetterDoctor does not collect information from children under the age of 13 in accordance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”). If you are a parent or legal guardian of a minor child, you may, in compliance with the Terms of Use, use the Services on behalf of such minor child. Any information that you provide while using the Services on behalf of your minor child will be treated as Personal Information as otherwise provided herein. If you are under the age of 18, you should not, and have no permission to, use the Services. 

## 2\. Information You Submit

We may store the information you submit to or through use of the Services. We use the information to fulfill your requests, provide Service functionality, improve Service quality, personalize your experience, display relevant advertising, provide customer support, send messages to you, back up our systems, allow for disaster recovery, and comply with legal obligations. Among the information you submit to or through the Services, please note: 

#### 2.1 Account registration

You must provide a valid email address in order to sign up for an account through the Services. In addition, you may provide us with your (1) full name, (2) phone number, (3) address, and (4) insurance data (such as insurance carrier and insurance plan). When you sign up for a BetterDoctor account, we opt you in to receive emails from BetterDoctor by default. You can manage your email preferences and modify some of the information associated with your account here (Link to my profile page). Note that you cannot opt out of receiving required administrative or legal notices. If you feel that an unauthorized account has been created depicting you or your likeness, you can request its removal by sending email to [privacy@betterdoctor.com](mailto:privacy@betterdoctor.com). 

You can also sign up by logging into online accounts you may have with third party service providers, including social networking service providers ("SNS") (e.g. Facebook); each such account, a "Third Party Account", via our Services as described below. As part of the functionality of the Services, you may link your BetterDoctor Account with Third Party Accounts, by allowing BetterDoctor to access your Third Party Account, to the extent permitted under the applicable terms and conditions that govern your use of each Third Party Account. If you chose to login through a Third Party Account, the login process will be governed by the terms and conditions imposed by the applicable SNS. 

You represent that you are entitled to grant BetterDoctor access to your Third Party Account, without breach by you of any of the terms and conditions that govern your use of the applicable Third Party Account and without obligating BetterDoctor to pay any fees or making BetterDoctor subject to any usage limitations imposed by the applicable SNS. If you decide to register by logging into a Third Party Account via our Services, we may obtain the personal information you have provided to the applicable SNS. Depending on the Third Party Accounts you choose and subject to the privacy settings that you have set in such Third Party Accounts, you understand that by granting us access to the Third Party Accounts, we may also have access to the information in your Third Party Accounts. To the extent permitted by your Third Party Account settings, BetterDoctor may pre-populate your BetterDoctor registration with Content from your Third Party Account. For example, if you choose to login to BetterDoctor through Facebook, the login authentication occurs between you and Facebook; BetterDoctor may obtain any information that you have authorized Facebook to provide. Please review SNS terms before using these shared login services. Such SNS have different terms of use and different protections for your content and personal information. 

#### 2.2 Public Content

Any information that you may reveal in a rating or review posting or other online discussion or forum is intentionally open to the public and is not in any way private. You should think carefully before disclosing any Personal Information in any public forum, and do not have permission to disclose any Individually Identifiable Health Information in any public forum. What you have written may be seen and/or collected by third parties and may be used by others in ways we are unable to control or predict. 

#### 2.3 Contacts

You can invite friends, colleagues, health care providers, and others whom you know (collectively, “Associates”) to join the Services by providing their contact information, or by allowing us to use your address book from your computer, mobile device, or other websites or services. We may also use publicly available information to suggest Associates whom you may want to invite to join the Services. If you invite an Associate to join and connect with you through the Services, we may use and store your Associate’s contact information long enough to process your requests. The names and email addresses of Associates whom you invite will be used to send your invitations and reminders as well as to allow BetterDoctor to help expand your network. We may include names and pictures of other people your Associate might know on BetterDoctor. The invitation will also give your Associate the opportunity to opt out of receiving other invitations to join BetterDoctor. 

When you send an invitation to connect to an Associate or another User, that Associate or User will have access to your email address because it is displayed in the invitation. The invitation may also contain other Services Content about you, such as your name and photograph, to help the User or Associate identify who is sending the invitation. Your BetterDoctor connections will also have access to your email address. You may not invite anyone you do not know and trust to connect with you. We may offer tools to help you upload your Associates' contact information so that you can find your Associates on BetterDoctor, and invite Associates who do not use BetterDoctor to join. 

#### 2.4 Messaging

If we incorporate, messaging into the Services, and you exchange messages with others through the Services, we may store these messages in order to deliver them and allow you to manage them. Many communications you initiate through BetterDoctor (e.g., an invitation sent to a non-User) will list your primary email address and name in the header of the message. Messages you initiate may also provide aggregate information about your network (for instance how many people are in your network), but will not list the people to whom you’re directly connected. If you send information from the Services to your phone via SMS text message, we may log your phone number, phone carrier, and the date and time that the message was processed. We will not charge you for sending information to your phone, but carriers may charge recipients for texts that they receive. 

## 3\. Third Parties

We do not rent, share, sell or trade Personal Information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. That said, we work with third parties and they may have access to some of your information: 

#### 3.1 Sharing of information

We share certain categories of information we collect from you in the ways described in this Privacy Policy. We may share Demographic Data with advertisers and other third parties only on an aggregate (i.e., non-personally-identifiable) basis. We may also share your Contact Data, Demographic Data, Insurance Data and Medical Data with health care providers you choose to schedule through our Services. We also share Personal Information and Traffic Data with our business partners who assist us by performing core services (such as hosting, billing, fulfillment, or data storage and security) related to our operation of the Services and/or by making certain interactive tools available to our users. Those business partners shall be bound to uphold the same standards of security and confidentiality that we have promised to you in this Privacy Policy, and they will only use your Contact Data and other Personal Information to carry out their specific business obligations to BetterDoctor and to provide your requested medical care and services. 

#### 3.2 Service Providers

We outsource some of our technical and customer support, tracking and reporting functions, quality assurance testing, payment processing functions, and other services to third parties. We may share information from or about you with them so that they can perform their services. 

#### 3.3 Business Transfers

We may share information from or about you with subsidiaries, joint venturers, or other companies under common control, in which case we will require them to honor this Privacy Policy. If another company acquires BetterDoctor or all or substantially all of our assets, that company will possess the same information, and will assume the rights and obligations with respect to that information as described in this Privacy Policy, unless we notify you otherwise. 

#### 3.4 Links

The Services may contain links to unaffiliated third party websites. Except as set forth herein, we do not share your Personal Information with them, and are not responsible for their privacy practices. We suggest you read the privacy policies on all such third party websites. 

#### 3.5 Health Care Providers

Health care providers, their employees, and their agents should be particularly aware of their obligations of patient confidentiality, including without limitation their obligations under the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (“HIPAA”), both in communicating with BetterDoctor and in responding to a review of their services posted through our Services. BetterDoctor does not have, and will not accept, any obligations of confidentiality with respect to any communications other than those expressly stated in this Privacy Policy and BetterDoctor’s Terms of Use. 

#### 3.6 Third Party Services

You can connect your BetterDoctor account to Third Party Accounts, in which case we may collect and store information identifying your account with the Third Party Account. We use the information to help you connect and share public content with your friends and followers. We may use the information to pre-populate your account registration information or identify others you may know or wish to invite to join the Services. 

## 4\. Use and Disclosure of Your Information

#### 4.1 Customization and Contact

One goal in collecting Personal Information from you is to provide an efficient, meaningful, and customized experience. For example, we can use your Personal Information to: (a) help make the Services easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once; (b) help you quickly find information and services; (c) help us create content that is most relevant to you; and (d) alert you to new information and Services that we offer. 

We may use your Contact Data to send you information about BetterDoctor or our products or Services, to contact you when necessary, including to remind you of upcoming or follow-up appointments, and in conjunction with your use of certain interactive tools. We may use your Demographic Data, Traffic Data, your Insurance Data or your Medical Data to customize and tailor your experience on the Services, in emails and in other communications, displaying content that we think you might be interested in and according to your preferences. You agree that BetterDoctor may use Personal Information to allow your health care providers to make appointments with other doctors on your behalf through the Services The sole purpose will be the booking of appointments, and health care providers will not transmit any information regarding the provision of health care. 

#### 4.2 Change in Control

We may also disclose your Personal Information and other information you provide to a third party as part of a sale of the assets of BetterDoctor, a subsidiary or division, or as the result of a change in control of BetterDoctor. Any third party to which BetterDoctor transfers or sells BetterDoctor’s assets will have the right to continue to use the Personal Information and other information that you provide to us, but they will still have to honor the commitments we have made in this Privacy Policy. 

## 5\. Changing and Deleting Your Information

As a registered User of the Services, you can modify some of the Personal Information you have included in your profile or change your username by logging in and accessing your account. Upon your request, BetterDoctor will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete your account and the Personal Information in your profile; however, it may be impossible to remove your account without some residual information being retained by BetterDoctor. When you delete your account, you understand that removed Content may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time (but will not be available to others). Furthermore, to the extent Content about you has been shared with others, or other Users have independently uploaded and/or retained Content about you, such Content may also remain on the Services. 

For example, while we will remove your account profile and the ability for others to contact you through the Services or access your Personal Information, some Content about you may be retained in the individual pages for health care providers you contacted through the Services or outside the Services. Such Content may be in aggregate form, such as data pertaining to the number of Users who accessed the respective health care provider’s profile, or in individual form, to the extent that the health care provider has entered or retained Content about individual patients. The respective health care provider is the only User who would have access to such retained aggregate or individualized Content. 

Registered users who wish to close their account should request removal by sending email to [privacy@betterdoctor.com](mailto:privacy@betterdoctor.com). 

## 6\. Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. For example, when you enter sensitive information through our Services, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

Although we make good faith efforts to store Personal Information in a secure operating environment that is not open to the public, you should understand that there is no such thing as complete security, and we do not guarantee that there will be no unintended disclosures of your Personal Information. If we become aware that your Personal Information has been disclosed in a manner not in accordance with this Privacy Policy, we will use reasonable efforts to notify you of the nature and extent of the disclosure (to the extent we know that information) as soon as reasonably possible and as permitted by law. 

## 7\. Updates and Changes to Privacy Policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the Privacy Policy will govern our use of your Personal Information and other information and will be located at http://betterdoctor.com/privacy. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by email or by posting a notice on or through the Services. By continuing to access or use the Services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy. 

## 8\. Contact

If you have any comments, concerns or questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@betterdoctor.com](mailto:privacy@betterdoctor.com). 

Last Updated on February 21, 2012 

Copyright 2016 BetterDoctor, Inc. All rights reserved.
